Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
‪[dramatic music playing]
‪[whispering] Jo.
‪[music softens]
‪Things could have ended
‪way differently for the both of us.
‪But you…
‪you thought. and you believed
‪that you knew better.
‪And look where that got you.
‪You motherfucker!
‪[music continues]
‪[cries. sniffles]
‪-[cassette rewinding]
‪-[screams]
‪-[car horns honking]
‪-[music stops]
‪[executive] Joyce. you've been amazing
‪as our brand ambassador.
‪[Joyce chuckles]
‪But you're not really delivering. girl.
‪to our contractual agreement.
‪It's two posts per month.
‪Only one of them requires you
‪to have Mr. Gomora in them.
‪It shouldn't be that difficult.
‪Maybe it's time for Ivory Oasis Baths
‪to move on with another influencer.
‪[chuckles]
‪Trinity… [chuckles]
‪I understand your concerns. believe me.
‪But. unfortunately. my husband
‪has been swamped with a lot of work. So…
‪[both moaning]
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪Because we've been hearing rumors.
‪-Oh.
‪-Mmm.
‪[lover] Gomora. [moans]
‪I don't know what rumors
‪you're talking about.
‪because my husband and I
‪have never been happier.
‪Actually. our marriage
‪has never been stronger. you know?
‪-Mr. Gomora.
‪-[breathing heavily]
‪[Joyce] Trinity. listen.
‪my husband and I. this coming Friday.
‪will be celebrating our 20th anniversary.
‪-Hmm? An entire 20 years.
‪-Oh.
‪And we've decided
‪to have a small celebration.
‪So I think it would be lovely
‪to have you there.
‪[both breathing heavily]
‪[Joyce] ‪To celebrate with us
‪and have a good time.
‪so you can see for yourself that…
‪there's nothing to worry about at all.
‪Everything is going well.
‪-[Trinity] Mmm.
‪-Hmm?
‪Well. if you say so.
‪I guess we'll see you
‪and your husband over the weekend.
‪Spectacular.
‪[both breathing heavily]
‪-[glass shatters]
‪-[both moan]
‪[upbeat music playing]
‪-[music stops]
‪-[breathes sharply]
‪[suspenseful music playing]
‪[Joyce] Gomora!
‪-Jo!
‪-Listen. listen.
‪This thing of yours. of just showing up
‪at my house as you please
‪is starting to annoy me.
‪You little skank.
‪Let me make this very clear.
‪-Mm-hmm.
‪-This is my house.
‪and that man you've decided
‪to shack up with here.
‪and spread your legs for.
‪is also mine.
‪I still have the keys to this house.
‪I can do as I please.
‪Jo!
‪My goodness. Jonasi.
‪Joyce.
‪Wow.
‪And here's the man of the moment.
‪Here.
‪Do you remember you promised me
‪that on our 20th anniversary.
‪we would renew our vows?
‪That time is now.
‪[scoffs] You're joking. right?
‪That invitation you're holding
‪has been sent to the relevant people.
‪And the tailor already has
‪your measurements.
‪-[Jonasi] Tell me you're joking.
‪-Oh. and I've decided
‪to invite you too. you cheap little whore.
‪I just want you to taste opulence.
‪since it's clearly not up your alley.
‪[Jonasi] Joyce.
‪-My love.
‪-Mmm.
‪[Jonasi] Please give me a few minutes
‪to deal with this.
‪[Jonasi] Mmm.
‪-[lover] Okay. my love.
‪-[Jonasi] All right. Mmm.
‪-Damn. you look hot in that dress.
‪-[chuckling]
‪Mmm.
‪Tell me. have you lost your mind?
‪I've worked so damn hard.
‪building all of this.
‪Especially my brand deal with Ivory Oasis.
‪-[groans]
‪-So you will show up
‪-to the celebration…
‪-[scoffs]
‪…whether you like it or not.
‪Pay attention. It's over. Joyce.
‪Anyways. I've spoken to your barber.
‪And I told him to arrange with Buhle
‪to get things organized.
‪-Wow.
‪-They'll let you know
‪when you can come and…
‪prepare yourself.
‪For our anniversary.
‪[scoffing]
‪Joyce. Joyce!
‪[car door opens. closes]
‪-[engine starts]
‪-[scoffs]
‪[upbeat music playing]
‪[Joyce] Make sure you're recording.
‪Okay. Sophie.
‪I need for everything to be perfect.
‪Perfect is your flowers
‪flying in from Kenya. darling.
‪-Ma is going to be involved. right?
‪-No.
‪-So she can choose her tier.
‪With all due respect.
‪my husband is Jonasi. okay?
‪-Come on. Joyce.
‪-No. Ma.
‪-This is our 20th anniversary.
‪-Oh. really?
‪[Joyce] So you've used place mats
‪rather than table sets?
‪Yes. place settings.
‪-options on the serviettes.
‪-Okay.
‪-[Sophie] What do you think. Mama Grace?
‪-This is the fruit cake?
‪Absolutely.
‪This one is perfect for Jonasi.
‪Because it's old and traditional.
‪just like him.
‪Actually. my husband
‪is a fan of chocolate cake.
‪so can we have that?
‪Hmm?
‪Mmm.
‪Wow. these are gorgeous.
‪I love them. all of them.
‪They're beautiful.
‪You know what I'm thinking?
‪I'm thinking. let's try
‪something youthful. you know?
‪When my husband looks at me.
‪I want him to remember
‪the good old varsity days.
‪-[chuckles]
‪-Well. lot has changed since then. Joyce.
‪[music stops]
‪[stammers] Cut.
‪Can you give us a moment. please?
‪Really. Mom?
‪My child.
‪Are you sure about all of this. though?
‪I'm sure.
‪[sighs]
‪[Joyce] ‪So. yeah. Let's talk. guys.
‪Tell me everything that you want to see.
‪Are you guys liking
‪my Ivory Oasis content?
‪SINDI_WA_STYLE
‪CAN I PLEASE HAVE THE LOCATION
‪Are you guys tuned in?
‪Oh. so what really is the key
‪to a happy marriage?
‪Hey! You're coming in hot. [chuckles]
‪It takes commitment.
‪We choose each other.
‪As well as also inviting God.
‪you know. to be a part of our family.
‪Hallelujah.
‪"This year you're celebrating
‪your 20th wedding anniversary…
‪TSIDIII:_
‪WOW MAMA JOYCE YOU ARE GLOWING
‪…what can we expect?"
‪THAN.DO5788
‪WE ALSO WANT THE SOFT LIFE
‪Joyce Gomora. extraordinaire.
‪lover of fine things. [chuckles]
‪[upbeat music playing]
‪-Okay. [chuckles]
‪-You go. girl.
‪[both vocalizing]
‪Tonight it's going to be lit.
‪I'm telling you.
‪-Who's this?
‪-[all laugh]
‪You look nice.
‪Thank you. Menzi.
‪-Ma. we're going out.
‪-Hmm?
‪Oh. you're going out. Where to?
‪Come on. Remember. you said
‪if I ace my Biology. we get to go out?
‪I'm joking. I remember.
‪But now why are you in such a hurry?
‪Sarah. She saw my status
‪and asked that we pick her up.
‪Okay.
‪And since your cousin
‪asked you to pick her up.
‪did she get permission from her mother?
‪Well. I have to ask
‪because you know how strict Essie is.
‪I don't know.
‪All I know is if I don't fetch her.
‪she'll be blowing up my phone
‪all night long.
‪-which I don't need.
‪-And what about your brother?
‪Menzi?
‪-[Menzi groans]
‪-[Joyce] Hmm.
‪Come on. Ma. We'll be out until late.
‪Oh. come on.
‪Mpume. why do you like doing this?
‪Why do you like acting as if
‪you're older than your brother. though?
‪Mom.
‪please don't make me take him with me.
‪[Joyce] Well. listen.
‪there's only one rule.
‪It's either you go with your brother.
‪so he can have fun too.
‪and enjoy life a little.
‪or you're all staying in
‪and calling it a night.
‪So take your pick.
‪[door slams]
‪[breathes shakily]
‪[Grace] You look so beautiful. my girl.
‪-[pensive music playing]
‪-Oh. you're so beautiful.
‪What's wrong. Joyce?
‪What is it?
‪Jonasi wants a divorce.
‪Joyce. this man moved out a year ago
‪from this house.
‪You can't be surprised. my dear.
‪No. Ma.
‪[maskandi music playing]
‪[slurring]
‪Being a man is so difficult. [groans]
‪-[gate closes]
‪-Alcohol…
‪-[dog barking]
‪-Uh…
‪-Shit.
‪-You.
‪You're not going to sleep in this house.
‪You'll go back
‪and sleep where you were drinking.
‪No. no. no. The thing is. my dear mother.
‪-firstly. I'm too annoyed to argue.
‪-[scoffs]
‪Secondly.
‪you are the last person
‪to judge me who I sleep with.
‪[mother] You're lucky I gave birth to you.
‪Otherwise. I would've strangled you
‪long time ago.
‪[son groans]
‪-Leave me alone.
‪-Oh. no. No.
‪Wait a minute. where are you off to
‪dressed like that?
‪Oh. Ma. we're going out.
‪-With who?
‪-With Mpume. We're just going to dance
‪-and have a good time.
‪-Sarah.
‪I told you to stop hanging with
‪these kids. they're not your type.
‪-[Mpume] How are you?
‪-We're fine.
‪Listen. Ma. I promise
‪to bring her back at 10:00. sober.
‪9:00. not 10:00. 9:00.
‪-You can go.
‪-[Mpume] Okay. Ma.
‪-Goodness.
‪-At 9:00!
‪[Mpume] All right.
‪[son] Oh. wow!
‪-Nice wheels! What?
‪-[Mpume] Come on. Free.
‪-Guys. where is my invite?
‪-[car door closes]
‪[grunts. laughing]
‪Hey. Menzi. Mamma's boy.
‪Tell me. where is the party happening?
‪-Oh. we're going to see DJ--
‪-[both] Uh-uh. no. Menzi.
‪Really? What does that have
‪to do with you. Freedom?
‪-You just need to back off.
‪-[groans]
‪-Freedom. just let the kids go. man!
‪-Let me see. What have we got here?
‪How about a little beep?
‪-[horn honks]
‪-[both laugh]
‪-[Freedom] Piss off!
‪-[Mpume] Bye-bye!
‪-Okay. Sure. yeah. See you all.
‪-Bye-bye!
‪-Jonasi. Jonasi!
‪-[phone rings]
‪Uh. Mrs. Gomora. I wasn't expecting you.
‪Buhle. I need to see my husband.
‪Uh. he's busy in the boardroom.
‪He's busy getting ready to…
‪Getting ready for what?
‪Um…
‪There's a celebration today
‪with the shareholders.
‪A celebration? Oh?
‪So I guess my invitation is still coming?
‪Hmm.
‪[Jonasi] Thank you.
‪You can leave it right there.
‪[Joyce] My goodness.
‪This looks like so much fun.
‪Alcohol? Must be nice.
‪-During work hours.
‪-What are you doing here?
‪I thought I should come and visit
‪Joyce's husband…
‪and look him dead in the eye
‪when I tell him he's got some nerve.
‪Joyce. listen. This is the only way
‪for you and I to move forward.
‪Listen. Jo? You see this?
‪I will not sign this nonsense of yours!
‪Are we clear?
‪You don't have a choice.
‪I will not lose the one thing
‪I've worked so hard for in my life.
‪-Do you hear me. Jonasi?
‪-Joyce. you don't need that.
‪-I'll take care of you.
‪-You?
‪-You'll take care of me?
‪-Yes.
‪Is this what you call taking care of me?
‪Is that what you call it?
‪Jonasi.
‪I'm the one who helped you
‪build all of this
‪for twenty years. Jo. Twenty years!
‪I've given you my whole life.
‪but you chose to throw all of that away.
‪all of this for that slut.
‪just for some ass.
‪You need to leave.
‪I'm not going anywhere.
‪You can't get rid of me.
‪-I'm here to stay.
‪-I'll call security.
‪Go ahead and call them.
‪Buhle!
‪Jonasi. what have you become? Tell me?
‪What are the kids going to say
‪about what you've become?
‪Get her out.
‪-Ma'am. please come with me.
‪-No! Don't you dare.
‪Shut up.
‪All of you. stop it!
‪I'm far from being done with you. Jonasi.
‪[exhales sharply]
‪I know my way out.
‪[Jonasi] Uh. Joyce.
‪You're forgetting something.
‪[dramatic music playing]
‪[Joyce clicks tongue]
‪[screams]
‪[breathing heavily]
‪["Ngibolekeni" playing]
‪[people kissing]
‪[moans]
‪You know I have to leave soon. right?
‪Oh. come on.
‪[lover] I told you
‪I have to go to the gym tomorrow.
‪Are you coming with?
‪Mm-mmm. Mpume will drop me off.
‪-All right.
‪-Mmm.
‪-[friend] Well. then. travel safe.
‪-My king.
‪-All right. man. Cool. bro.
‪-As always. my boy.
‪-[Mpume] Bye. X. [chuckles]
‪-Bye. Take care.
‪-Bye-bye. [kisses]
‪-These two really look good together.
‪[chuckles]
‪-[Mpume] Lindani.
‪-What? That's my man.
‪Okay. tell me.
‪Aren't these bottles expensive?
‪I don't know. I guess.
‪[Lindani]
‪Are you here to do a price check.
‪or drink alcohol?
‪-Hey. piss off!
‪-Come on. man. Come on. big guy.
‪I'm not here to cause a commotion.
‪big guy.
‪There's something really important
‪I have to handle in there.
‪I think my girlfriend is in there
‪having a good time with another man.
‪Please let me in. you know?
‪[grunts] Please. my brother.
‪Here's to life. and here's to money!
‪Leave this here.
‪the life of the party has arrived.
‪-Take this. Me-Me. There we go.
‪-[laughs]
‪Guys. is this your little party?
‪-Freedom. what are you doing here?
‪-Oh?
‪-[Mpume] Menzi called him.
‪-Mm-hmm.
‪Come on. guys. we're here to have fun.
‪-not bombard Freedom with questions.
‪-[laughs]
‪Cheers to that!
‪[dance music playing]
‪My brother's here.
‪[grunts]
‪Uh. okay. boundaries. I know.
‪Um. I'm sorry.
‪[chuckles] What's wrong with you?
‪So what's your excuse
‪for not going there to talk to her?
‪No. Why?
‪I mean that girl over there.
‪It's obvious that you like her.
‪Freedom. you're out of your mind.
‪That's my sister's friend.
‪-[laughing]
‪-She's like a sister to me.
‪-Why are you laughing?
‪-Shame.
‪-What's funny? I'm serious. Eish.
‪-Come on. man. Meaning. huh?
‪You know what the funny thing is?
‪You look really scared.
‪But you know what? Relax. boy.
‪The doctor is here.
‪Doctor Freedom. boy.
‪You see.
‪I have something special for you. my dawg.
‪Something to help you.
‪Oh. my goodness.
‪what are you doing? [chuckles]
‪This will help you so that you can relax
‪and enhance your mood.
‪Loosen up a little bit.
‪-so you can feel good. you know?
‪-Mm-mmm.
‪So you can build the courage
‪and go talk to her. you know?
‪-Take some of this. my boy.
‪-Mm-mmm. I do not do drugs. my brother.
‪Oh. come on. man. Just say. "Ah."
‪-No. no. no.
‪-Hey. I said. "Ah!"
‪Do you wanna talk to her or don't you?
‪-[sighs] Freedom. my brother…
‪-I said. "Ah!"
‪-Okay. then. "Ah."
‪-"Ah." There we go.
‪[laughing] Let's start this party!
‪-[Mpume] Yes!
‪-[Lindani] Cheers to life!
‪[breathing heavily]
‪[distorted audio]
‪[distorted indistinct dialogue]
‪[breathes heavily]
‪[no audible dialogue]
‪-What are you trying to do?
‪-No!
‪-No! No!
‪-What are you trying to…
‪[Menzi]
‪Hey. hey! Didn't you hear the lady?
‪-[groans]
‪-I'll kill you. you son of a bitch.
‪-I'll kill you!
‪-[Mpume] Menzi! Menzi!
‪-Don't touch… Don't hold me!
‪-[patrons screaming]
‪-Get your hands off my brother!
‪-Fuck you! Let go of me!
‪Let go of me! Don't touch me! [grunts]
‪[bouncer] Hey! What the hell is going
‪on here? What are you people doing?
‪-Hey! Hey! Get the hell out of here!
‪-Ah! Leave us alone!
‪-Fuck off!
‪-[clamoring]
‪You think I'm afraid of you?
‪-Ah. no!
‪-Fuck off!
‪[clamoring]
‪-Let's go!
‪-[Menzi] Screw you guys!
‪-Let's go! They'll find us here. boys.
‪-Menzi.
‪Thank you so much
‪for being my Superman tonight.
‪[exclaims]
‪That's what I'm talking about. my boy!
‪[exhales sharply]
‪[shoes thud]
‪[phone buzzing]
‪Sophie.
‪Is the anniversary party canceled?
‪Why are you asking me that?
‪What have you heard?
‪Well. someone called me and told me
‪Mr. Gomora is flying out to Zim tomorrow.
‪Who told you that?
‪Well. is he leaving?
‪[breathes sharply]
‪Sophie. I'll get back to you. okay?
‪I'm a bit busy right now.
‪[phone beeps]
‪[thuds]
‪-[exhales sharply]
‪-[glass thuds]
‪Jo?
‪[both moaning]
‪[Joyce] Jo?
‪[thuds]
‪[gasps]
‪-Wow. [gasps]
‪-Do you like it?
‪[Joyce] Mm-mmm. I don't like it.
‪-Huh?
‪-I love it. I love it.
‪-[Joyce] Thanks. I love it.
‪-I almost fainted. Don't play with me.
‪[Joyce] ‪I love you even more.
‪[Jonasi] ‪I love you.
‪-Mm-mmm. not here.
‪-What is it? Come on.
‪The kids are going to walk in on us.
‪Oh. wow.
‪What…
‪[gasps]
‪[dramatic music playing]
‪[both moaning]
‪-[shrieks. gasps] Shit!
‪-[shatters]
‪[breathing heavily]
‪Oh. sh…
‪Oh!
‪[moaning continues]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today